Tatiana Cherbaeva Front-End Developer

+1-310-994-49-76

✓ tatianacherbaeva@gmail.com

O Los Angeles, CA

in LinkedIn

GitHub

Profile

I am a self-motivated, effective, and professional Front-end Engineer with over 2 years of experience specializing in JavaScript, React & NodeJS. Willing to learn additional languages and skills based on work demand.

Eager to expand my skill set to improve efficiency and productivity, I am seeking a position with a company that offers opportunities for growth and long-term skill development.

Skills

Programming

JavaScript (ES5, ES6), HTML5, CSS3 (Flexbox, Grid, Sass)

Frameworks | Libraries

React (Redux, React-Router, Redux Toolkit, Context API), TypeScript, DOM, NodeJS, Bootstrap, Material UI, Formik, Reactstrap

Development Utilities

GitHub, Git, VS Code, JIRA, Figma, Heroku, Trello, Chrome DevTools, Debugger, Unit Test

Professional Experience

2021 – present Chicago, IL

Front-End Developer

Cargo Fleet

- Developed front-end part of fleet management application with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React and JavaScript.
- Developed and implemented highly responsive components using React and Redux.
- Developed authorization and pagination features.
- Provided assistance on fixing bugs or fixed bugs presented in code.
- Attended meetings in a timely manner to explain my task progress, provided and received feedback on the accomplished work. Used JIRA to track, report and audit the issues in the application.
- Took full responsibility and management of the tasks assigned.
 Technologies used: ReactJS, Redux, Yarn, ES6, CSS3, Git, Heroku

2020 – 2021 Los Angeles, CA

FREELANCE Front-End Developer

Design and code whole applications for professional web projects. Apply expert knowledge of JavaScript, HTML, DOM, and CSS to deliver advanced user interfaces and controls with scalability in mind. Build theming system for web applications using Shopify and other platforms fitting each client's need. Effectively manage all projects from start to finish. Links: www.gardenborn.com 🗷, www.oliviacare.com 🗷, www.mydanktank.com 🗷

Education

2021 – 2022	Software Engineer Bootcamp Seytech
2019 – 2020	Software Engineer Bootcamp freeCodeCapm
2005 - 2011	Bachelor's degree, Industrial and Organizational Psychology Saint Petersburg State University